<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pari</title>
    <link>https://pariari.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pari</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 17:12:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pariari.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 18:27:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Pari is an artist-run space where people and communities come together to talk, think, learn and do. Art and artists are at the core of Pari’s activities: we believe that artists play a vital role in processing and reflecting the important issues of our time. Reflecting the social, the political and the deeply personal, our program draws out ideas that are particular to our location in Western Sydney on unceded Darug land, and that resonate well beyond the local.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Business 2</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/programming/06-mixedbusiness2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/programming/06-mixedbusiness2/</guid>
      <description>Mixed Business may feel a little different this year. Last year, we gathered in 40 degree heat, our souls fed in this space through art, community, and, of course, good food. Over the course of the past year, our senses of time and place were discombobulated. The places where we gathered shifted as we re-adapted, and continue to adapt, to what will become a well-versed adage known as “unprecedented times.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemonade</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/programming/05-lemonade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 15:12:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/programming/05-lemonade/</guid>
      <description>Bitter and sweet, nostalgic and transformational, Lemonade is making the best of your circumstances; it is transforming adversity into something beautiful that can be savoured and shared. It is persistence, self-care, wry humour and generosity. This lemonade is not saccharine — there’s always that hint of acid, of something sharp and honed — but the edges are softened and warmed over time.
Lemonade is a bit old wisdom, a bit Beyoncé, and all fresh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports Show</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/programming/04-sportsshow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 15:12:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/programming/04-sportsshow/</guid>
      <description>Coming in to bat next is Sports Show 🏆 Connecting an all-star lineup of seasoned players and rookies, Pari presents live commentary of the on-and-off field behaviour of sport – the highs and lows, wins and losses.
We’ve smashed our salary cap with this one with support from City of Parramatta.
The game of the season that’s not to be missed. Just another day in #parradise 🏈
In lieu of a regular opening, we will be meeting in Parramatta Park between 2-4pm on Sunday 13th September, where we can keep a safe distance and hopefully get some sun (it&amp;rsquo;ll be postponed if it rains).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Companions</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/programming/03-companions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 12:06:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/programming/03-companions/</guid>
      <description>In Companions, materials are active partners in each practice, and the subsequent works are collaborations: the result of a push and pull between human and non-human companions.
The artists in Companions choose to work with materials and processes that are not stable or fixed. Things that respond, often unpredictably, to light, air and time. Some of the materials are living, and continue to grow and morph. Others will dry, decay or eventually die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>P2P</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/p2p/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 12:06:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/p2p/</guid>
      <description>P2P is a program of virtual sharing between Pari and artist-run collectives and spaces around the world. Through a series of online workshops with friends near and far, we hope to collectively engage with ideas and models for collaboration and criticality within and beyond the arts.
For this first iteration, Pari has teamed up with Gudskul and The White Pube to host the following workshops online:
Gudskul workshop: Speculative Collective</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Business</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/programming/02-mixedbusiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/programming/02-mixedbusiness/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago, it seemed like mixed businesses were on almost every street corner in Parra. They’re still here, mostly in the surrounding suburbs: next to roundabouts, between apartment blocks and houses mid-renovation. Little family-run businesses stocking contradictory products side-by-side on rickety shelves. Some tins host dust and dead bugs; other shelves are perpetually empty, signalling what’s important to the 100 people in the immediate area.
Pari invokes the mixed business as a mode of operation, for multiplicity and exchange: a cornerstore(stone) for community and convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 From 5</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/5from5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 18:27:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/5from5/</guid>
      <description>Details coming soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pari 2021–2022 Callout</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/callout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 18:27:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/callout/</guid>
      <description>This is the callout for artists and curators who are keen to work with Pari in 2021–2022.
Please read through our guide for more information about what we&amp;rsquo;re looking for and what we provide.
If you have questions or concerns, please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to email us at hello@pariari.org Applications due by 11:59PM, Friday 26 February  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Degrees Hotter</title>
      <link>https://pariari.org/programming/01-10degreeshotter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pariari.org/programming/01-10degreeshotter/</guid>
      <description>10 Degrees Hotter was almost the name of this gallery but we couldn’t all agree. Some thought it sounded like a boy band, others thought it was a mouthful. The phrase came out of a way of describing the conditions of being in Western Sydney— on any regular summer day, it can be five to ten degrees hotter in the west compared to out east. This artificial climate is created by the urban heat island effect, where hot air gets trapped in the vast concrete expanse between the mountains and the coast.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
